People want to believe they want to believe that they that they have conceded to and that they recognize the horror that is slavery.
And obviously, unequivocally, they would have been against that.
They would not have been somebody saying, but the South relies on that.
Oh, this is a big business. This is the industry. What are they going to do?
But they would say that because, in fact, present day of slavery is a system and by which a person is held, held against their will.
They are denied of their freedom and their civil liberty and forced to produce to use their labor and produce goods for the money for somebody else.
That's that's slavery. Dave, that's what we've got.
That is what we've got. We have two million people incarcerated in this country.
Four hundred thousand of those people have not even had a trial.
All of those people are being forced.
They are forcibly held and they are being used to make money for the state and they are being disenfranchised.
That is slavery.